jellyfish.co.uk 2017-11-25

# Privacy Policy | Jellyfish UK

### **At Jellyfish Group Ltd. we respect your privacy and we promise to:**

  * Use your personal information only to provide you with the information you have requested or have agreed to receive.
  * Keep your data safe and secure and process it in a manner that follows your wishes.
  * Use cookies and web beacons (but only those which don't personally identify you) to improve the quality and relevance of the messages we send you.
  * Assist you to change your mind at any time about the communications you have signed up to receive.
  * Only disclose your data to third parties for marketing purposes when you have said it's OK to do so.

##   
 **About Jellyfish Group Ltd.**

Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd's registered address is Jellyfish House, 31 London Road, Reigate, Surrey RH2 9SS. The registration number is 03845245.  
Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd is part of Jellyfish Group Ltd.

## What data we collect

We collect your Full Name, Email and Phone on our website Contact Us form. We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to the information you voluntarily give us. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

## Where your data is held

Your data is held on secure servers operated by Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd in the UK, and will be stored under the robust security measures described below.

Data security

When you give your personal data to Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd we will process that data in accordance with our responsibilities under the Data Protection Act 1998, and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and other relevant legislation.  
We will keep your data safe and secure. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct usage of information, we monitor and adjust our physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure your personal data while in our care, or in the care of any outside suppliers with whom we may contract to process your data on our behalf. Any outside suppliers are under strict contractual terms to mirror the security policies that we currently have in place.

What we do with your data  
We will process the data you supply in order to provide any service you have requested when you sign up on our website. We will only use your personal data for the purposes you have permitted and we will not share it for marketing purposes outside of Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd. unless you have given us permission to do so. If this practice changes in the future, we will update this policy to identify the non-agent third parties and include customer opt-out information.  
________________________________________  
How we use cookies  
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  
We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  
If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.________________________________________  
Messages on our websites from third parties  
We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.________________________________________  
Links to other websites  
Our website may provide links to resources that we believe to be useful. These links will lead you to websites operated by third parties that operate under different privacy policies. Should you choose one of these links you will be leaving the Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd site for a site over which we have no control.  
________________________________________  
Updating & accessing your information  
You have a right under Privacy Shield to see what information we hold about you, subject to certain conditions. If you want to exercise this right, you should make an application to us in writing. We may ask you to provide us with sufficient information so that we can be sure of your identity. If you would like to proceed with a request to see what data we hold about you, please write to:

### The Data Protection Compliance Officer 

Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd  
Jellyfish House  
31 London Road  
Reigate, Surrey, RH2 9SS

We hope you will benefit from any communications we send to you, but if at any time you change your mind, you may unsubscribe to our email or mobile messaging by following the instructions we give you at the time we broadcast a message to you. If you have given us permission to write to you or to phone you with marketing messages, you may change your mind by writing to:

### The Data Protection Compliance Officer

Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd  
Jellyfish House  
31 London Road  
Reigate, Surrey, RH2 9SS

If we do not hear otherwise from you, we will assume that the information you provide to us is accurate and up-to-date and we will continue to use the information to send you any communications you have requested.

## Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.

## We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

## Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.  
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.  
You can change your personal information by emailing us.

## Privacy Shield Compliance

Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd and its wholly subsidiaries Jellyfish Group Ltd and [Jellyfish Dynamix](https://www.jellyfishdynamix.com/) comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd at: 

Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd   
250 South President Street   
Suite 10   
Baltimore, MD 21202   
hello@jellyfish.net  
443-842-5555 

Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles to BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint. 

Finally, and under limited circumstances, EU individuals with unresolved complaints may direct them to the Privacy Shield Panel, a binding arbitration mechanism. 

The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over our compliance with the Privacy Shield, and is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission. Jellyfish Online Marketing Ltd may be required to disclose personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We acknowledge our potential liability in cases of onward transfers of Privacy Shield data to third parties.
